# JUNIPER STANLEY

## **UI/UX Designer**

928-710-6413 juniperstanley7@gmail.com

Denver, CO

Open to remote positions

## **UI/UX Skills**

- Style Guides
- Prototyping
- Social Media Kits
- Employer Branding
- Adobe/ Sketch/ Figma/ HTML
- Content Marketing
- App/ Website/ Logo Design
- Sustainability and Accessibility centered

## **SUMMARY**

UI Designer with specialty in empathizing with clients and development of user- centered systems. Experience with 20+ design projects, focused on clean, simplistic aesthetics that communicate boldly and effectively. Utilizes several design systems, i.e. Sketch, Adobe, Figma, HTML. Committed to the leveling up of alternative agriculture and sustainability industries and overall care of the global community.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **UX/UI Designer, Self- employed, Remote (Present)**

Duties included: Branding, Web/UX/UI Development, Logo Design Handy-person, Self Employed, Prescott— 2021- 2022 (Present)

Duties included: General handiwork skills, plumbing, electric.

## Patient Care Advocate, SWC Prescott, Prescott, AZ — 2017-2020

Duties included: vast cannabis and medical law knowledge, educational services, sales, customer care, operation of POS systems.

## Owner/ Operator at-home bakery, Prescott, AZ — 2017-2018

Duties included: marketing, baking, catering, online orders, general business operation.

#### **EDUCATION**

**Career Foundry, UI Design 2021** 

Yavapai College, CNA Associate's Program, 2012-2016

## **CURRENT PROJECTS**

**Communal- Community Building App** 

**Pocket Prosperity- Finance App** 

**Heim-Recipes App** 

## **PROFESSIONAL LINKS**

Behance: https://www.behance.net/juniperdesigns

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/alexia-juniper-stanley-68944a160/

Website: <a href="https://juniper-designs.webflow.io">https://juniper-designs.webflow.io</a>